Guide to the thinkBIG: A Conference on International Women's Health and Human Rights Collection SC0927
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
thinkBIG: a conference on international women's health and human rights collection
2008
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Associated Students of Stanford University. Speakers Bureau
SC0927
0.5 Linear Feet (2 boxes)
Collection includes a conference packet containing the attendee booklet, tickets, and several flyers; and 5 videodiscs: Session 1 Girls' Education, Session 2 Women and HIV/AIDS, Session 3 Reproductive Health, Session 4 Violence Against Women, and the finale keynote panel. Speakers on the keynote panel were Stephen Lewis, Dr. Eunice Brookman-Amissah, Fiona Muchembere, Esta Soler, and Anne Firth Murray.
Information about Access
This collection is open for research.
Associated Materials
Poster from the event can be found in the Stanford University Archives Poster Collection under the number Po2008-007.
Biographical/Historical Sketch
thinkBIG was a student-run conference held at Stanford University on February 1-3, 2008, which aimed to inspire students to action by critically looking at the health situation of women and girls in poorer countries.
Description of the Collection
Collection includes a conference packet containing the attendee booklet, tickets, and several flyers; and 5 videodiscs: Session 1 Girls' Education, Session 2 Women and HIV/AIDS, Session 3 Reproductive Health, Session 4 Violence Against Women, and the finale keynote panel. Speakers on the keynote panel were Stephen Lewis, Dr. Eunice Brookman-Amissah, Fiona Muchembere, Esta Soler, and Anne Firth Murray.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Administrative transfer Office of Student Activities, 2009; Women's Community Center, 2016.
Women -- Health and hygiene.; Girls -- Education.; Lewis, Stephen; Brookman-Amissah, Eunice.; thinkBIG: A conference on international women's health and human rights (2008: Stanford University); Soler, Esta.; Murray, Anne Firth.; Muchembere, Fiona.; Associated Students of Stanford University. Speakers Bureau
- Records (Box 1)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2016-101
  - Session 1: Girls' Education (Copy 1), 2008 Feb 2; 1.01; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 1, Compact disc 1)
  - Session 1: Girls' Education (Copy 2), 2008 Feb 2; 1.02; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 1, Compact disc 2)
  - Session 2: Women and HIV/AIDS (Copy 1), 2008 Feb 2; 1.03; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 1, Compact disc 3)
  - Session 2: Women and HIV/AIDS (Copy 2), 2008 Feb 2; 1.04; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 1, Compact disc 4)
  - Session 3: Reproductive Health (Copy 1), 2008 Feb 2; 1.05; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 1, Compact disc 5)
  - Session 3: Reproductive Health (Copy 2), 2008 Feb 2; 1.06; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 1, Compact disc 6)
  - Session 4: Violence Against Women (Copy 1), 2008 Feb 2; 1.07; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 1, Compact disc 7)
  - Session 4: Violence Against Women (Copy 2), 2008 Feb 2; 1.08; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 1, Compact disc 8)
  - BIG Finale: Keynote Panel (Copy 1), 2008 Feb 2; 1.09; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 1, Compact disc 9)
  - BIG Finale: Keynote Panel (Copy 2), 2008 Feb 2; 1.10; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 1, Compact disc 10)